romsmode.com 2019-12-12

# Privacy Policy - RomsMode.com

## Collection and use of information

In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information:

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website.

Use of cookies - When you visit www.RomsMode.com, we send one or more cookies - a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies contain information that can later be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user account details, preferences and tracking user trends. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, www.RomsMode.com features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

Log information - When you use www.RomsMode.com, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. Also we may collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the links you click and other actions taken in connection with www.RomsMode.com sites and services. We also collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring Web site addresses.

www.RomsMode.com processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America and in other countries. In some cases, we process personal information on a server outside your own country. We only process personal information to provide our own services. Also, we are using Google Analytics and Yandex Metrika.

## Choices for personal information

When you sign up for a particular service that requires registration, we ask you to provide personal information. If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use.

If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent.

## Proprietary Rights

  * the Website, the Website owns, solely and exclusively, all rights, title and interest in and to The Website;
  * you can also use the Advanced Search feature to search the entire website;
  * all the content, data and materials thereon, the look and feel, design and organization of The Websiter;
  * the compilation of the content, data and materials on The Website, including but not limited to any copyrights, and other intellectual properties and proprietary rights.
